(Amy:)There's a craft and folk
art museum on Wilshire.
(Penny:)Well, that's Wilshire's problem.
Come on, you know, there-there's
(Penny:)got to be something fun we could
do that the guys will hate.
(Leonard:)Hang on, why do we
have to hate it?
Three words:
Doctor Who convention.
I-I did not force you
to go to that.
(Penny:)You walked out of the house
in a fez and bow tie. I went
(Penny:)so you didn't get beat up.
(Leonard:)I wasn't gonna get beat up.
(Penny:)You were, but somehow
I held myself back.
(Sheldon:)You know what you could
make us do? Ice-skating.
(Sheldon:)The cold air will trigger
Leonard's asthma
(Sheldon:)and it plays right into
my well-known fear of
(Sheldon:)getting flattened by a Zamboni.
(Leonard:)Now you're helping them
find ways to make us miserable?
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm sorry, Leonard, I'm a
problem-solver, it's what I do.
(Amy:)I actually can't
go ice-skating.
(Amy:)I have unnaturally
brittle ankles.
(Penny:)Is there any part
of your body that's normal?
(chuckles)